Hello.
こんにちは
How old are you now?
今、おいくつですか?
I'm 20 years old now.
今、20歳です
20 years old.
20歳
Are you a student?
学生ですか?
No, um, I work at a bed shop.
いえ、えっと、ベッドショップで働いてるの
Bed shop?
ベッドショップ?
yes.
はい
That's it.
あれだね
Doesn't that mean you're attracted to animals?
なんか動物うったりってことよね?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうです
How long have you been doing this?
どれくらいやってるんですか?
About 2 years.
2年くらい
This is right after shooting.
こう、撮影してすぐじゃん
It would be nice to have a Tiny like this.
こんなティニーさんいたら、いいね、
Looks like I'll buy it.
買っちゃいそうだね
But I guess that's it, I guess it's families.
でも、あれかな、やっぱ家族連れとか、
Are there many couples or other customers?
カップルとか、お客さん多いのかな?
There are many.
多いです
Hey, that's it.
ちょ、あれだね
Even though I came here to buy a pet,
せっかくなんかペット買いに来たのにさ、
I wish I had this cute Tiny.
この可愛いティニーさんいたらちょっと、
I'm in trouble.
困っちゃうな
Customer side too
お客さん側も
Hey, are there any popular ones that sell well?
ね、 なんか売れるというか、人気なやつとかあるんですか?
Is that a cat?
あれ、猫だっけ?
Short legs and fluffy.
足短い、ふわふわの
I've seen it on YouTube.
YouTubeで見たことある
It's kind of popular, isn't it?
なんか人気だよね、あるね
cute.
かわいい
It flows well.
よく流れてくれるね
Is it short?
ショートだっけ?
It's toddling and cute.
よちよちして、かわいいってやつだね
Do you like munchkins?
マンチカン好きなんすか?
I like munchkins.
マンチカン好きですね
Do you buy Tiny-san yourself?
ティニーさんとかって自分でも買ったりするんすか?
Like my store.
自分の店舗とか
I don't buy it, but anyway, I'm still at the store even if I don't buy it.
買わないけど、でもあれか、買わなくてもお店にいるもんね、
There's a cute girl.
かわいい子がね
But who are the animals in the store?
でもお店にいる動物って誰だろうね、
Children or something.
子供とか
Yeah, it's small.
うん、ちっちゃい
It's small, but when it grows up,
ちっちゃいからね、育っちゃうと、
It seems like something has changed.
なんか変わっちゃったみたいな
The color may change.
色が変わったりする
The color also changes.
色も変わるんだ
Brown.
茶色が
That's right, it's not a chicken, but it does change.
そうなんだ、鶏じゃないけど、変わったりするんすね
Even though I used white, brown was mixed in.
白やったのに、茶色が混じってきたりとか
Hey,
へー、
What do you think?
どう なんすか?
It's tiny, it's tiny.
ちっちゃい、ちっちゃいんですよね
It looks small and cute.
ちっちゃくてかわいいらしい
It really does look like a small animal.
なんか本当に小動物とかのような感じですね
It's pretty small, isn't it?
結構ちっちゃいとか、ちっちゃいよね
It's small.
ちっちゃいです
How many are there?
いくつあるんすか?
He is about 145 years old.
身長は145歳くらい
145?
It's not 50.
50じゃないんだ
What does being small mean to you?
ちっちゃいのっていうのは、自分の中ではどうなんすか?
A complex or something like that is a plus.
コンプレックスとか、なんかプラスに
gap?
隙間?
Yeah, I'm stuck in a gap between trains.
うん、電車の隙間にはまっている
But on the other hand, I feel like I'm going to be crushed.
でも逆に押しつぶされちゃいそうだよね
I don't have a clothes size.
服のサイズがない
Isn't it S?
Sじゃないんすか?
Even S is big.
Sでも大きいんですよ
It's tough.
大変だね
Something like XS.
XSとか
Oh, it's going to be child-sized.
ああ、子供サイズになるね
The child size is small.
子供サイズはちっちゃいんですよ
It's still different.
まだちがうんですね
Please come behind me for a moment.
ちょっと 後ろもくぐってもらって
I want it.
ほ しい
It's so small.
ち っちゃいね
Can I have you face me?
こっちじゃあ向いてもらっていいですか?
Can I have you turn the pages a little more slowly?
ちょっとゆっくりめくってもらっていい?
It's like it's spinning.
回っちゃうみたいな
On the side, yeah.
横に、そうそう
Does your body shape never change?
ずっと体型変わらない?
No change.
変わらない
Wouldn't it be smaller?
もっとちっちゃかったりしないの?
primary school.
小学校
Elementary school, elementary school.
小 学 校、小学校
By my senior year, I was already pretty good at it.
もう高学年くらいで結構出来上がったりしてた
more.
もっと
Not much has changed since I was in 6th grade.
小6くらいからあんまり変わってない
That's right.
そうなんだ
A long time ago.
ずっと前の方に
I wish I was this cute when I was a student.
学生の時とかさ、 こんな可愛かったらさ、
Don't you have any time?
なんか時間とかされない?
It won't happen.
されないですね
In the countryside.
田舎で
That's right.
そうなんだ
There are no such people.
いないんだ、そういう人
Whether it's in the countryside or the boss.
田舎でも、ボスでも
I can sit comfortably.
すっきょん座れるんで
If you're in trouble, you're probably going to get kicked out.
困ってたらされるんじゃないのね
If there wasn't anyone there.
人いなかったらね
It's noticeable.
目についちゃうんだね
You can take this off and use it as underwear.
これ脱いで下着になれる
yes.
そう
Don't you usually eat anymore?
普段もう食べない?
Eat.
食べます
Do you mean you exercise?
運動とかしてるってこと?
I don't.
しないです
Is everyone in your family skinny?
家族みんな細いの?
no.
いや
It's thick.
太いです
It's very thin.
めっちゃ細いね
I'm jealous.
うらやましい
Slowly behind.
ゆっくり後ろ
She also has breasts.
おっぱいもあるんだね
He's a really nice buddy.
本当にすっきりナイスバディだよね
Looks like it'll be handy.
手がきそうじゃん
I was surprised.
びっくりしちゃったわね
I'm starting to get curious.
気になってきちゃった
Is your stomach getting bigger?
お腹が大きくなってんの
I wonder if my complexion will change today.
顔色はめるかな、今日
I feel like I'm going to be sucked in.
吸い込めれちゃいそう
I can't help it because I'm worried about my tongue.
舌が気になっちゃってしょうがないんだよ
It's a really beautiful shape.
めっちゃ形きれいだよね
I have nothing to hide, so take a look.
隠すのもないんで、ちょっと見てよ
This blood vessel is so colorful.
この血管出てんのめっちゃ色いね
Raise your arms and hands.
腕、両手上げて
I don't like it.
嫌だ
why?
なんで?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
No armpit?
脇ダメ?
Yeah.
うん
tickles?
くすぐったい?
tickles.
くすぐったい
I absolutely hate it.
絶対に嫌だ
絶対嫌だ
Are your boobs good?
おっぱいはいいの?
Yeah, I don't like my armpits.
うん、脇は嫌だ
I understand.
分 かった
I know it's bad for my armpits.
脇ダメだって分かるさ
Can I look at you?
こっち見ていい?
Yeah.
うん
Turn around a little and stick your butt out.
ちょっと後ろ向いて、 お尻突き出してみて
Tikkui butt.
てっくぃーってお尻
Can you see this one too?
こっちの方も見える?
It's smooth.
つるつるだね
yeah?
ん?
slippery.
つるつる
Then turn to me and take off your panties.
じゃあこっち向いてパンツ、 脱いで、
Well, let's just sit there.
じゃあそのまま座っちゃおうか
So I'll open it again.
で、また開いてもらう
Do you understand the letter M?
M字って分かる?
Ass, up to this point.
お尻、この辺まで
yes.
はい